foreign
[Music]
they are talking about their Hobbies
I'm glad we finally get to catch up
me too
how have you been
I've been good
just busy with work you know
I know the feeling
what have you been up to in your free
time
well I've been really into woodworking
lately
I've been making some furniture from my
apartment
I made a coffee table and a bookshelf
it's been really satisfying to see
something I made with my own hands in my
home
that sounds amazing
I've always wanted to try woodworking
but I don't know where to start
it's easier than you think
I watched some YouTube tutorials
there are also some beginner woodworking
classes you could take
that's a good idea
maybe I'll look into it
what about you
do you have a favorite pastime
I love painting
I've been doing it since I was a kid and
it's something that always relaxes me
that's great
what kind of painting do you do
mostly watercolors
I love the way the colors blend together
do you have any of your paintings
hanging up in your apartment
yes I do
I've also given some as gifts to friends
and family
that's really cool
have you ever thought about selling your
paintings yes I have I would feel so
proud of myself if a gallery asked me to
expose some of my paintings that's for
sure
how often do you paint
I try to paint at least once a week but
it depends on my schedule
it's important for me to make time for
it
I've been so stressed at work lately
my hobby helps me relax
I bet
do you have any other Hobbies
yeah I also play guitar
I've been playing for about 10 years now
that's awesome
do you write your own songs
I do
I've written a few but I mostly play
covers
I sometimes play at family gatherings
that's really cool
I'd love to hear you play
sure
what about you
do you have any other Hobbies besides
painting I also love hiking
I try to go on a hike at least once a
month that sounds nice
do you have a favorite hike
yes there's one that goes up to a
waterfall
it's about a two hour hike but it's
worth it for the view
that sounds amazing
let's go hiking together sometime
that would be fun
foreign